Vernon, Florida is a documentary film directed by Errol Morris.
Early Errol Morris documentary intersplices random chatter he captured on
film of the genuinely eccentric residents of Vernon, Florida.
A few examples?
The preacher giving a sermon on the definition of the word "Therefore," and the obsessive turkey
hunter who speaks reverentially of the "gobblers" he likes to track down and kill.
Himself, played by Albert Bitterling.
Himself, played by Roscoe Collins.
Himself, played by George Harris.
Vernon, Florida is a 1981 American documentary film produced and directed by Errol Morris
profiling various residents living within the town of Vernon, Florida.
Originally titled Nub City, this follow-up to Gates of Heaven initially focused on residents of
the Southern town who cut off their own limbs as a way to collect insurance money.
After Morris's life was threatened by the subjects of the
film, he re-worked Nub City into Vernon, Florida.
The film explores themes of florida, small town, eccentric, 1980s.